http://wdt.net/site/privacy.html

NNY Newspapers Archives
WDT Historical Archive (1870–1922)
Home
Use of this Website Constitutes Acceptance of our Privacy Policy and User Agreement.I. GeneralNNY360, publisher of NNY360.com, and its parent corporation, the Johnson Newspaper Corporation, and its affiliates are committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using NNY360.com. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit NNY360.com. This Website (the "Website") is owned and operated by NNY Newspapers ("we," "us"), a division of the Johnson Newspaper Corporation. This Website's Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") describes how we use, share and protect the personal information that we collect through this Website. This Policy addresses our privacy practices relating to general and registered use of the Website by visitors located within the United States. This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference and is an integral part of the Terms and Conditions set forth in the "User Agreement" that governs your access to and use of the Website. If you have not already reviewed the User Agreement, please do so now. If you cannot or do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website.II. Your Consent to This Privacy PolicyYour access to and use of this Website is subject to this Privacy Policy. By using our Website, or providing information to us, you agree and consent to our collection, use, disclosure, processing, transfer and use of information for the purposes set forth in this Policy, including but not limited to the transfer of your Personal Information between our Service Providers, affiliates and subsidiaries in accordance with this Policy. Any access to such information will be limited to the purpose for which such information was provided to our affiliate, subsidiary or Service Provider.This Website may contain links to Web sites that are owned and operated by unrelated third parties in the United States or elsewhere. This Privacy Policy does not apply to personal information collected on any third-party Website. In most cases, third-party Websites have their own policies regarding privacy. We recommend you review the privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal information about yourself.If you do not consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy, you should not access or use this Website.III. The Type Of Information That The Website CollectsGeneral Description"Personal Information" is information that can be used to identify or contact you, such as your name, postal address, email address, credit card number, telephone number and similar information. Such information identifies you personally, either alone or in combination with other information. We collect only Personal Information that you provide to us by using our Website. Such information includes information automatically transferred by your computer and information that you knowingly enter in registration forms, applications, and other documents such as when you register for access to a restricted area of the Website intended only for registered users who pay a fee for access.If you wish to access a restricted area of the Website, to register, you must provide us with certain Personal Information, including your name, e-mail address and postal mail address. We will use this Personal Information to review and verify your registration information. We may also use your Personal Information to notify you of any changes to this Policy. You can always opt-out of receiving communications from us by following the "opt-out" procedures set forth on our Website.Information You Provide to UsWe collect the Personal Information you voluntarily provide when you use a limited access portion of this Website. For example, the information that you provide when you become a registered member and create an account, purchase products, subscribe to e-newsletters, or send us questions and comments is information that we may collect. This information may include, for example, your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, information about your organization, credit card information, and information about your purchases.Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser-Usage DataWe collect information that is sent to us automatically by your Web browser. This information typically includes your IP address, the address of the Web page you were visiting when you accessed this Website, the name and version of your operating system and browser, and the date and time of your visit. We collect and store this information to measure the Website's performance and improve the Website's design and functionality. We may share this information with third parties to illustrate how the Website is used and for other marketing purposes, to improve the Website's design and functionality, statistically evaluate Website usage, or customize our Website's content, layout and services.Cookies and Clear GifsWe use "cookies" to collect information and support certain features and functionality of this Website. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web server or that is stored in your computer's memory for the duration of your visit. For example, we use cookies to collect statistical information about the ways visitors use this Website — which pages they visit, which links they use, how long they stay on each page and how often they return. This information is known as "click-stream information" and does not include your Personal Information.If, however, you have created a user identity on one of your visits to this Website (for example, by creating an account), we may link the information collected by cookies to information that identifies you personally. When you log into our Website, your registration ID number, e-mail address, name and other information may be stored in a cookie and used to customize your experience on the Website.If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. You may also delete our cookies as soon as you leave this Website. Although you are not required to accept our cookies when you visit this Website, if you set your browser to reject cookies, you will not be able to use all of the features and functionality of this Website.The Website may also use clear gifs (also known as "web beacons") in combination with cookies, to help Website operators understand how visitors interact with the Website. A clear gif is typically a transparent graphic image (usually 1 pixel by 1 pixel in size) that is placed on the Website, which allows the Website to measure the actions of a visitor who opens the page that contains the clear gif. We use clear gifs to measure traffic and related behavior, and to improve your experience when visiting the Website. We also use clear gifs to manage the content available on the Website.The information provided by your browser and stored in our web server logs does not identify you personally. We use this non-personal information primarily to create statistics that help us improve this Website and make it more compatible with the technology used by our visitors. In addition, under appropriate circumstances, for example, if we receive a subpoena or suspect fraud, we may share our server logs — which contain visitors' IP addresses — with law enforcement authorities or others who may use that information to trace and identify individuals.To "opt-out" of (a) receiving communications from NNY360 (except for communications necessary for your use of the Website), (b) having your personally identifiable information disclosed to third parties for marketing purposes, or (c) any other consent previously granted for a specific purpose concerning your personally identifiable information, send an e-mail to NNY360 at online@wdt.net.IV. Our Use and Disclosure Of InformationIn addition to the uses described throughout this Privacy Policy, and subject to applicable law, we and our Service Providers (as described below) may disclose your Personal Information to:Our Service ProvidersNNY360 contracts with service providers who use cookies to track and analyze usage and volume statistical information, and monitor responses to e-mail and advertising campaigns. The information obtained from cookies is used to administer the Website, improve the quality of your experience when visiting, and monitor the effectiveness of our marketing activities. Data collected by third parties from this Website is owned and used by NNY360, but is accessible by such third parties. NNY360 may share your personal information with, for example, companies that help process credit card payments. Our service providers are required by contract to protect the confidentiality of the personal information we share with them and to use it only to provide specific services on our behalf.Third PartiesNNY360 does not share e-mail and postal mailing lists with any other organizations in addition to those expressly stated herein. NNY360 does not sell or rent telephone numbers, e-mail addresses or fax numbers of registered users or others who communicate contact information to it or whose contact information has been otherwise obtained by NNY360.Business TransfersInformation submitted through this Website is a business asset of NNY360 and will become part of its normal business records. Your Personal Information may be transferred to another entity (either an affiliated entity or an unrelated third party) in connection with a merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar corporate event. In the event of a merger, liquidation, dissolution, or sale or transfer of substantially all of the assets of NNY360, Personal Information and/or Usage Data collected from you or about you may be sold, assigned, or transferred to the party acquiring all or substantially all of the equity and/or assets of NNY360 to permit the party to continue the operation of the Website, including the restricted areas. Subject to your ability to opt-out, by using this Website and submitting your information to us, you consent to the sale and transfer of your Personal Information as described in this paragraph.Government and Legal DisclosuresWe may disclose the Personal Information we collect through this Website, when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law (or a court order or subpoena), to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft, to enforce our Terms and Conditions or other agreements that govern your use of this Website, or to protect the rights, property or safety of NNY360, our members or others.V. Third-party AdvertisersWe may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website. These companies may use information (not including any Personally-Identifying Information) about your visits to the Website and other websites that are contained in Web Cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Using a tool created by the Network Advertising Initiative, you can opt out of several third-party ad servers' and networks' Web Cookies simultaneously. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit any of the following sites: http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp, http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/, or http://www.aboutads.info/choices/. Please contact us if you would like to know the identity of the third-party advertising companies we are currently using to serve ads.We may allow advertisers to choose the characteristics of users who will see their advertisements, and we may use any of the Non-Personally Identifying Information we have collected (including information you may have decided not to show to other users, such as your birth year or other sensitive personal information or preferences) to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements. We do not identify you to the advertiser.VI. Click-Through AgreementsBefore you may use certain areas of this Website, you may be asked to indicate your acceptance of certain special terms and conditions by clicking on a button marked "O.K." or "I agree." Any special terms and conditions to which you agree will supplement and amend this Privacy Policy, but only with respect to your use of those areas of this Website.VII. Privacy NoticesThis Privacy Policy may be supplemented or amended from time to time by "privacy notices" posted on this Website. For example, certain pages of this Website contain privacy notices providing details about the personal information we collect on those pages, why we need that information, and choices you may have about the ways we use that information.VIII. The Choices You HaveNNY360 respects your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use and disclose your Personal Information. We generally ask you to indicate your choices at the time and on the page where you provide your Personal Information.You may browse this Website without providing any information that identifies you personally and may choose not to provide the information we request, although this may mean that you can not make a purchase or take advantage of other features of this Website.You may cancel your registration to any part of the Website at any time by following the appropriate instructions contained on the Website.IX. Unsolicited Comments and FeedbackUnless subject to a separate agreement between you and NNY360, any feedback, data, answers, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas or the like (collectively, "Feedback") that you send to us through this Website will be treated as non-confidential and nonproprietary. We assume no obligation to protect such Feedback from disclosure and are free to reproduce, use and distribute the Feedback to others for any purpose and without restriction. By submitting Feedback through this Website, you are granting NNY360 a non-exclusive, unrestricted, perpetual and irrevocable license to use your Feedback and any related know-how for any purpose whatsoever, without compensating you in any way, including, but not limited to, developing and marketing products and services incorporating such Feedback.X. SecurityWe use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving payment data. We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of personal information that we have collected from or about you. We are in compliance with the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act for any data that we may collect that is subject to this regulation. It is important that you understand, however, that no Website or database is completely secure or "hacker proof." You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse, for example, by protecting your passwords.We take seriously the security of the information we collect. NNY360 has therefore implemented technology and security policies and procedures intended to reduce the risk of accidental destruction or loss, or the unauthorized disclosure or access to, such information, reasonably appropriate to the nature of the data concerned. If we believe that the security of information that you have provided to us has been compromised, we may notify you by e-mail, if we have your email address.XI. Changes And Updates to This Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy, at any time and without prior notice, by posting a revised version of this Privacy Policy on the Website. The revised version of the Privacy Policy will be effective as of the date that we post it on this Website. Your use of this Website following a revision of the Privacy Policy constitutes your agreement that all Personal Information collected from or about you through this Website after the revised Privacy Policy is posted is subject to the terms of the revised Privacy Policy. We urge each visitor to refer back to this page regularly and especially prior to providing or updating any Personal Information. This Policy may not be otherwise amended without the written consent of NNY360.You may access the current version of this Privacy Policy at any time by clicking on the link marked "Privacy Policy" at the bottom of each page of this Website.XII. Our Policy Regarding Children and MinorsThis Website is not directed at minors (under the age of 13) or generally intended for use by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children in this age group. We ask that if you are a minor you not submit any personal information to us. If your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the Website, they may receive unsolicited messages from other persons. Please tell them not to do so.
Latest News
Chemical contamination found in Oswego High School’s Wilber Field soil
Trinity UMC offers pizza coupons for Canale’s through Human Concerns office
Oswego County police departments work on reinventing the police
Public Record Oswego County Police Blotter
St. Lawrence County virtual tasting series launches Tuesday with In-Law Brewing
Undeterred by pandemic, ‘Getting Ahead’ program graduates newest local cohort
Ogdensburg mayor says budget cuts are not the salvation city needs
Champion board sets zoning law public hearing
Most Popular
Watertown state trooper suspended after being charged with sexual abuse, burglary, DWI
Parts of St. Lawrence County moving toward possible microcluster declaration
Felts Mills man recounts night he was shot in his home
Cuomo warns of ‘tremendous’ tax increase to offset state’s budget gap
One Ogdensburg councilor leaves Monday’s City Council meeting early after clashing with mayor
Classifieds
111 - AAA ABES
AAA BRZOSTEKS.COM Auctions-Antiques/ Businesses/ Farms & R.E. 1-800-562-0660. Commission low
BRZOSTEKS.COM REAL Estate Auction Co. Inc.- Homes, Estates, Farms, Commercial
FOR SALE premium Soybean & Alfalfa baleage, $80/per bale, whole
GoCo Massena, LLC was formed on October 29, 2020. The
STATE RT 177
INEXPENSIVE Cars and Trucks. Starting at $2,995. 2008 Honda Odyssey
SUPREME COURT STATE OF NEW YORK COUNTY OF ST.
NEW IDEA manurer spreader, EC, Ford 600 tractor w/5' brush
POMERANIAN PUPS ready 12/23 male, black chocolate markings, vet checked
Locally reported news and sports
Stay Current with What's Happening
Get the most of NNY360, register today!
Register
By providing your email address, you consent to receive emails and special offers from NNY360.com
Locally reported news and sports
Stay Current with What's Happening
Get Breaking News Alerts deliverd FREE to your inbox
Success! An email has been sent to
with a link to confirm list signup.
Error! There was an error processing your request.
News Updates
Please enter a valid email address.
Get the news I need
Manage my lists
By providing your email address, you consent to receive emails and special offers from NNY360.com
© Copyright 2020 NNY360, 260 Washington Street Watertown, NY | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
